(GRUNTS)
Parkour!
Michael.
Parkour! Parkour!
Extreme.
MlCHAEL: Parkour!
This is parkour.
lnternet sensation of 2004,
and it was in one
of the Bond films.
lt's pretty impressive.
The goal is to get
from point A to point B
as creatively as possible.
So technically
they are doing parkour,
as long as point A is delusion
and point B is the hospital.
(DWlGHT YELLS)
Parkour!
(DWlGHT WHOOPlNG)
DWlGHT: Yeah, parkour!
Andy, leap frog.
Go, go!
Do me! Do me!
Yeah. Okay. Yeah.
Parkour! Parkour!
Get off! Get off!
Okay.
Parkour!
Jump over
the camera.
Okay, we all go together,
or we go one at a time.
Here it is. Here it is.
Truck to refrigerators
to dumpster,
360 spin onto the palettes,
back flip, gainer
into the trashcan.
Yeah, gainer!
Yeah, yeah, yeah !
Parkour, parkour!
l'm right behind you,
Andy. Come on !
Let's do it!
Yeah !
ANDY: (GROANS) Parkour.
(lNAUDlBLE)
DWlGHT: Good.
Excellent.
Thank you.
Here you go.
ls there anything
else l can do?
Yes.
(CLEARlNG THROAT)
See those files behind
Kevin's desk?
Mmm-hmm.
Go put them all
in random order.
Okay.
DWlGHT: Then come back here
for your next assignment
concerning their order.
This is the last day
of our summer interns.
lt's been nice.
We haven't had
interns in a whiIe.
(lNAUDlBLE)
Ever since MichaeI's
Monica Lewinsky incident.
He didn't do
anything sexual.
He just made far,
far too many Monica
Lewinsky jokes.
lt was just easier for
corporate to shut down
the program.
Think she did him?
l bet there's
something there.
l was with them in
the kitchen yesterday,
and they were all too happy
to be cleaning the freezer.
lf they get married
before l do, l'm going
to kill myself.
Who's getting married?
Nobody.
lf somebody doesn't tell me,
l'm gonna start screaming.
lt's Eric and Megan.
Oh !
Hey, l hired them.
Matchmaker.
This place is like
Spaniard fly.
They're not getting married.
lt's just talk.
Did everybody know
about this but me?
There's nothing to know.
lt's just gossip.
Okay. Okay.
We haven't told anyone
that l'm pregnant.
What with her being unmarried,
knocked up by some guy.
The yakety-yaks in this office
would have a field day.
Yeah, and we don't
want them at the
wedding thinking
Jim's being marched
down the aisle by my
dad with a shotgun.
Wait, there's not going
to be a shotgun?
Nope.
No shotgun? Because
that changes everything.
Can't back out
now, Halpert.
What are you going
to do about it?
There's no shotgun, so,
free at last,
free at last.
No, keep it up.
You'll never guess
what l know.
Okay. Let me finish
this thought.
Eric likes Megan.
He most definitely does.
He's been asking her out
repeatedly for weeks.
She finally said yes.
They went out on a group
date the other night.
Apparently
it went very well.
How do you know this?
People tell me things.
l guess l have
a face you can trust.
l think it's because
of my low cheek bones.
And boom. Okay, what is it?
What can't l guess?
l hate, hate, hate
being left out.
Whether it's not being
picked for a team or
being picked for a team
and then showing up
and realizing that
the team doesn't exist,
or that the sport
doesn't exist.
l should have known.
Poopball?
Oh, man, l know
how you feel.
Third wheel.
l have been the third wheel
so many times in my life.
My mom told me something
once that made me
feel a lot better.
She said, "The third wheel
is what makes it a tricycle."
What are you
talking about?
l am talking about
your group date
with Megan and Eric.
At Tinks?
Yes.
How'd you know
about that?
Well. . .
Did Stanley tell you?
Stanley was on your
group date?
No. Stanley
was with his wife.
l waved at him
but he didn't wave back.
(CHUCKLES)
Does anybody else
know about this?
No.
(CHUCKLES)
There he goes.
So, what is the scuttlebutt?
Anybody hear anything?
Nothing? l got a little
something-something.
l don't know
if l should say.
So just keep it
to yourself, then.
Stanley is having
a midlife crisis.
Stanley is way past
the middle of his life,
especially considering
his height-to-weight ratio.
Well, apparently,
he and his wife
were out dancing
at a club
for young people.
Teri's out of town,
Michael.
Who?
Stanley's wife, Teri.
She's at an interior
decorating expo in Philly.
And Stanley hates crowds,
kids and music. l think you
should check your facts.
You stupid son of a bitch.
You set me up.
What are you
talking about?
Stanley's wife
is out of town.
He was with somebody.
He was definitely
with someone.
Oh ! Was he?
Well, who?
His sister?
(LAUGHS)
l don't get it!
lf that was his sister,
then what they were doing
was totally illegal.
Drugs?
Making out.
Okay.
No, it's okay.
Never mind.
Carry on.
(WHlSPERlNG)
Stanley is having
an affair.
What?
l know.
(lNAUDlBLE)
MlCHAEL: I am very happy
right now, thrilled perhaps,
to be a part of the office,
to be a part of
the conversation.
When you have somebody's
attention, and their eyes
are lighting up
because they are
very interested in
what you have to say,
that is a great feeling.
And I experienced that
firsthand today.
lt is wonderful to be
the center of attention.
MlCHAEL: That and that
are the same letter.
KEVlN: Q.
No. No.
Okay.
He's holding a pencil.
He could be doing
a crossword puzzle
with that pencil.
What's that letter,
right there? Same
letter here and here.
What haven't you guessed?
T.
T! Yes! Yes!
That is a T.
And there's another one right
there. Just sound that out.
You're almost there.
Hey, Stanley,
where are you going,
big guy? Up to no good?
l'm meeting a client.
Do you have a problem
with that?
No, no, no, no, no.
l just had a quick
question for you.
l'm casting a movie and
l'm looking for a woman who
can dance, beautiful woman.
Do you know anybody?
Goodbye.
Pays 5 million dollars.
Nudity required.
You have to stop this.
(WHlSPERlNG) Did you
hear that Stanley's
having an affair?
(WHlSPERlNG) l did.
From you. You got to
stop telling people.
Okay. l get it. You feel
out of the loop and you
feel sorry for yourself,
and it's really
sad because everybody
thinks you're a loser.
Do you even know
if it's true?
Do you have any idea?
Because you might be
ruining his life.
Hold up! Hold up! Hold up!
No, no, no, no!
(HONKlNG)
lt's time to stop being
polite and get real !
Stanley,
you having an affair?
That is ridiculous.
Of course not.
Why would you think that?
So it's not true.
Okay. Well. . .
(SlGHlNG) Oh !
Those interns, they told me
they saw you at the club,
and they all said
it was you.
lt was clearly just
racial profiling gossip.
The little. . .
Damn ! l told her
it was a stupid idea. . .
lt's so stupid.
. . .to go up in that club.
lt's just that Teri's been
traveling a lot lately.
l know. l know.
lt's been lonely.
Oh, l bet. l. . .
Cynthia's been
keeping me company.
She was my nurse
when l was
in rehabilitation.
We used to go
on these long walks
on the treadmill.
l didn't intend. . .
Wait, wait, wait.
So it is true?
Yeah, but Michael,
l'm going to go
break it off.
That's where l'm headed
right now. l swear.
Oh, my God.
Wait a second.
Do people often say
they're going on sales calls
and then go someplace else?
Because that's not cool.
l just need you to promise
not to say a word
about this to anyone.
Michael, please.
l'm not saying
a damn thing.
l'm counting
on you, Michael.
Okay.
You can count on me.
Oh, that smells good.
Yeah, l might have extra.
lt just depends
on how many l eat.
Did you hear about Angela?
That's pretty weird.
Yeah. What do you
mean exactly?
Well, the fact that
she apparently is dating
an 81 -year-old billionaire.
Owns a Quiznos
on the turnpike.
Really?
Uh-huh.
(EXCLAlMlNG) Right?
How do you
un-tell something?
You can't.
You can't put words
back in your mouth.
What you can do is
spread false gossip,
so that people think
that everything that's
been said is untrue,
including "Stanley
is having an affair."
lt's like the end of
Spartacus. l've seen that
movie half a dozen times,
and l still don't know
who the real Spartacus is.
And that is what makes that
movie a classic whodunit.
Kelly has
an eating disorder?
MlCHAEL: Yes.
She always
eats my lunch.
Anorexia.
She's an anorexitic.
We should do something.
Nothing can be done.
Just have to tell
everybody and hope
for the best, l guess.
l'm worried about Erin
because she's not
a very good worker.
l don't know how long
she's going to last here.
Really?
Yeah. So. . .
And Andy is gay.
Andy Bernard?
Mmm-hmm.
(WHlSPERlNG)
Did you hear
Pam is pregnant?
(WHlSPERlNG) Really?
Yeah.
She's going to hate
being a mom.
(KEVlN CHUCKLlNG)
What?
Tea.
So?
You would.
l like tea.
Oh, l bet you like it.
Yeah. l like it a lot.
l love tea.
Do you like it as much
as you like men's butts?
What?
Because you're gay.
Who told you that?
Was it Broccoli Rob?
Someone from Chi Psi?
Or did you run
into someone from
my high school?
This is not the first
time rumors about me
being gay have come up.
Twice before, actually.
Just a weird coincidence.
lt's a little too weird.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Almost makes you wonder
if it's not a coincidence
at all. Whoa!
Which it is, of course.
But it makes you wonder.
Did you hear the rumor
about me, that l'm gay?
l did, yes.
And?
What?
Do you think it's true?
Do you think that l'm gay?
Are you attracted
to other men?
(SCOFFlNG)
No.
But let me kick
you a scenario.
l'm at, like, a beach cabana
and Brad Pitt approaches,
tries to lean in
and kiss me.
l would definitely resist,
like, at first,
but if he was persistent,
l might give in a little bit
to just sort of see
what it felt like.
Would l push him away?
How hard? Like, what if he's,
like, really aggressive?
lf you resisted Brad Pitt
a little bit, he would
still need to get to you?
This is not real Brad Pitt,
this is, like, in my. . .
This is my fantasy.
Or it's, like, not fantasy,
it's, like, what l'm. . .
lt's just a scenario.
Well, l wish l could help you.
l don't. . . You might be gay.
You might be gay.
OSCAR: What exactIy
is my responsibility here?
To comfort insecure
heterosexual men?
That can't possibly
fall to me.
PHYLLlS: (SOFTLY)
How far along is Pam?
A few months.
That's why they're
rushing the wedding.
(SOFTLY) Guys, guys,
guys, you can't believe
everything you hear.
Like Stanley
having an affair.
That is crazy.
There's no stock in it.
lt's a weird day
for false facts.
Just let it go.
Okay, everybody, big day.
Last day for our interns.
Lot of other stuff.
Who knows what to believe?
Dwight, the honors.
Present these to the Dean
for credit. And as a gift,
l've attached my card.
Call me any time
of the day or night.
Why would we call
you at night?
Well, now you can't call me
at all, so problem solved.
You're going to regret that
when you find yourself
between a moose
and her cubs at night.
Look to the intern
on your left.
Now to your right.
One of you will do
exceedingly well in business,
just unlimited potential.
One of you
will make a living
and nothing more.
And one of you
will make
a great mother.
lt's up to you to choose
which you want to be.
l am so happy
you're eating again.
Me, too.
Tuna, how come you never
try to set me up?
l don't really do that.
But Pam might have
some friends, though.
Women friends?
Yeah.
Not guy friends?
Are you interested
in her guy friends?
No. l mean,
for the record,
l prefer women.
Okay.
But off the record,
l'm kind of confused.
Really?
Yeah, the evidence
is sort of stacked
against me, l feel like.
Well, you've got to
figure this out.
Yeah, right?
Yeah.
How?
You've got to have
sex with a woman.
Righto.
And then a man.
And then compare.
Oh !
All right.
Well, hey.
Yep.
Congratulations to you.
On what?
(CHUCKLES) Come on.
Little baby Tuna.
Little junior Toro.
You know, a baby
conceived out of wedlock
is still a bastard.
What?
Want me to say it again?
Why did that come
into your brain?
Can l talk to you
for a second?
So, they know.
Who did you tell?
l didn't tell anyone.
Nobody.
Hey, did one of you tell
Stanley that l have asthma?
Because l don't.
lf it gets out they
won't let me scuba.
lf l can't scuba,
then what's this
all been about?
What am l working toward?
What? You think
l'm the voice
of the Taco Bell dog?
What are you guys talking
about? l have a daughter.
How could l be a virgin?
Hey, has everyone heard
a crazy rumor about
themselves today?
ALL: Yes.
Yeah, yeah ! You know what,
let's discredit these rumors.
Yeah, sure, but who's been
saying all that stuff?
lt's not important, Jim.
l just think we shouldn't
listen to any of this crap.
Sure, but we should
get to the bottom of this.
Let's pick a rumor
and trace it back
to the beginning.
l need to do
mine first.
Who's been saying
that there's another
person inside of me
working me
with controls?
l heard that from Andy.
l heard it from Erin.
KEVlN: What?
l heard it from Michael.
Michael.
PAM: Michael?
He's over here.
Where are you going?
Nowhere.
Michael.
Hmm?
You told people that
l use store-bought manure,
when l showed you where
my manure comes from.
Hmm? Hmm?
Don't get on it.
Michael, don't.
PAM: Don't get on. Do not.
KEVlN: Michael, no.
Michael.
Stay, Michael.
Step away.
Stay.
ANDY: Come on, boss.
PHYLLlS: No. No.
Okay,
l made it all up.
KELLY: What?
Even the fact
that l'm gay?
Yes.
Yes!
But, guys,
l'm a victim here,
too. Okay?
People have been saying
that l'm a J.Crew model.
No, we heard
that about Jim.
Jim? No, no, l spread
the rumor that somebody
here was a J.Crew model
and l was referring
to myself.
How is that
a bad rumor?
Because a lot of people think
that models, even though
they're very attractive,
are somewhat vapid.
lt's set our industry
back quite a bit.
Michael, why? Why say all
these things? Why make up
an eating disorder,
Stanley's affair,
me being a spokesdog?
You told everyone
l was having an affair?
Okay, okay,
here's the thing.
There was one true rumor
out there today. l didn't want
everybody to know what it was,
so all of you
are off the hook except
for this one person.
Well, then what's
the one true rumor?
We have a right to know.
Michael, am l gay?
The one true rumor,
and this is going to ruin
this person's life, is that. . .
That Pam's pregnant.
ANGELA: l knew it, l knew it.
l knew it!
Her breasts were
a tiny bit bigger.
At first, l thought,
"Oh ! She has a new
bra with padding."
But then l thought,
"Pam doesn't need padding."
lt just didn't
add up, Jim.
Okay, thank you.
PHYLLlS:
Congratulations!
ERlN: That's really
great, you guys.
RYAN: Don't vaccinate it.
DWlGHT: Who's the father?
Jim.
CREED: How far along?
JlM: Four months.
Who's the OB-GYN?
Stop. Don't.
All right, you know, this is
not the truth and you can't
fall on the sword this way.
The real thing
is that Stanley Hudson
had an affair.
No.
Yes.
Thank you for trying
to defend us,
but actually Pam is pregnant
and we can prove it.
Yes.
lf everybody would like
to see the proof.
Wanna. . . Okay.
Okay.
We're just
going to wait here?
What's the proof,
l mean. . .
(lNDlSTlNCT CHATTER)
(ALL EXCLAlMlNG)
lt's true!
Pam, look at that!
That is the inside
of your vagina.
That's not how
it works but. . .
lt's clear why we were
trying not to tell people.
That's clear now. Yeah.
How long have you known
about the pregnancy?
A week? A month? A year?
Michael, we only told
our parents last week.
Did you pee on a stick?
l did. But it
was inconclusive.
You should have told me.
You're right.
We should have
realized that you are
an equal part of this.
(PHONE RlNGlNG)
Yes.
ERIN: Michael, Teri Hudson
returning your call.
(GASPS)
You called Stanley's wife?
Oh ! Oh !
Yeah, a long time ago.
Just to make sure
she was out of town.
Oh, God.
Don't take it.
No, l have to take it
or it'll seem suspicious.
lf you talk to her,
you're going to tell
her about Stanley
and that's going to
seem more suspicious.
No, no, no, l can do this.
You can't do this.
Yes, l can. l am going
to tell her that l need
to redecorate my condo
and l need her help.
We will haggle about money,
and l will back down,
and then l won't talk to her
until this whole
Cynthia thing has blown over.
JlM: Sounds terrible.
We think you should. . .
Michael, please don't.
(CLEARlNG THROAT)
Hey, what up, Cynthia?
Just hang on a second,
Cynthia.
Well, it turns out that
Teri was already suspicious
because she had caught Stanley
and Cynthia a few months ago.
So Stanley promised
that he would stop,
and he did. End of story.
Well, not exactly.
(lNDlSTlNCT SCREAMlNG)
Cynthia kept caIIing him.
She wouId not stop
calling him, and she
was in Iove with him.
And get this.
Cynthia, aIso married.
So, you can't stop Iove,
I guess.
And quite frankly,
I don't think
you should ever even try.
l learned that a company can
describe their internship as
full of exciting experiences,
even if that's a lie.
There's no regulation.
l learned that half these
people's e-mail password
is "Password."
l learned that a ream
of paper is 300 sheets.
l thought it was 500.
Oh !
l guess l didn't
learn anything.
l learned that if you
look even the tiniest bit
like Jet Li,
Michael will call you
Jet Li all summer.
Julia Stiles.
Alan Thicke.